Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. William Woodville Rockhill papers (MS Am 2121): Guide.
William Woodville Rockhill papers,
- I. Correspondence and other papers
  - Church, Samuel Harden, 1858- A.L.s.(S. H. Church) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Pittsburgh, 14 Feb 1896., (473); ([2]p.)
  - Church, Samuel Harding, 1858- Typed L.s.(S.H.Church) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Pittsburgh, 9 Jul 1897., (473a); 1l.
  - Church, Samuel Harding, 1858- Letter; 2 Sep. 1895., (474)
  - Church, Samuel Harden, 1858- A.L.s.(S. H. Church) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Pittsburgh, 25 Jul 1900., (475); ([2]p.)
  - Churchill, William, 1859-1920. A.L.s.(Willm. Churchill) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 1 Mar 1913., (476); 1l.
  - Clark, Arthur H. Typed L.s.(A. H. Clark) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Cleveland, 9 Apr 1914., (477); 1l.
  - Clark, Arthur H. Typed L.s.(Arthur Clark) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cleveland, 15 Jun 1914., (478); 1l.
  - Clay, Brutus J. A.L.s.(Brutus J. Clay) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Richmond, 10 Jun 1913., (479); ([3]p.)
  - Claypoole, Benjamin. Transcript of L.s.(Ben. Claypoole) to [George Claypoole]; London, 22 Mar 1706-1707., (480); ([2]p.)
    Enclosed: Mimeographed description of Letter s.(Jacob Rutgers Le Roy); Paris, 2 Jul 1890. 1l.
  - Claypoole, Benjamin. Transcript of L.(unsigned) to "Loving Cousin" [i.e. George Claypoole]; London, 22 Mar 1706., (481); 1l.
  - Claypoole, Benjamin. Transcript of L.s.(Benn. Claypoole) to [George Claypoole]; London, 22 Mar 1706., (482); ([2]p.)
  - Claypoole, David Chambers. Ms.L.s.(D. C. Claypoole) to [?]; Philadelphia, 22Feb 1826., (483); [2]p.
  - Claypoole, David Chambers. A. Account of services, of a military nature, rendered during the American Revolution; [n.p., n.d.], (484); ([3]p.)
  - Claypoole, David Chambers. A.L.(third person) to General La Fayettte; [n.p., n.d.], (485); 1l.
  - Claypoole, Joseph. A. Memorandum of marriage of James Claypoole and Holon Morror and a list of births and some deaths of their children; 1657 - 1678., (486); 2l.
  - Claypoole, Joseph. A. Memorandum of marriage of Joseph Claypoole and Rebecca Jennings and a list of births and some deaths of their children; Philadelphia, 1703- 1715., (487); [2]p.
  - Claypoole, Joseph. A. Memorandum of marriage of Joseph Claypoole and Rebecca Jennings; Philadelphia, 21 Dec 1710., (488); [1]p.
  - Cloud, Frederick D. A.L.s.(F. D. Cloud) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 5 Apr 1907., (489); ([4]p.)
    Enclosed: Typed (c.c.) of L.s.(F. D. Cloud) to Robert Bacon; [n.p.] 4 Apr 1907. 3l.
  - Cloud, Frederick D. A.L.s.(F. D. Cloud) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 7 Nov [1908], (490); ([4]p.)
  - Cloud, Frederick D. A.L.s.(F. D. Cloud) to [William Woodville]Rockhill; Mukden, 6 Dec [1908], (491); ([4]p.)
  - Cloud, Frederick D. Typed Copy of L.s.(Frederick D. Cloud) to [Charles] Denby; Mukden, 18 Dec 1908., (492); 4l.
  - Cloud, Frederick D. A.L.s.(F. D. Cloud) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 21 Dec [1968]., (493); ([4]p.)
  - Cloud, Frederick D. A.L.s.(F. D. Cloud) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 9 Jan [1909]., (494); ([4]p.)
  - Creelman, James. A.L.s.(James Creelmah) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 30 Dec 1895., (495); [2]p.
  - Cockburn, Henry. A.L.s.(Henry Cockburn) to [William Woodville]Rockhill; Chungking, 7 Aug [1889]., (496); ([7]p.)
  - Cockburn, Henry. A.L.s.(Henry Cockburn) to [William Woodville]Rockhill; [London] 24 Feb [1893]., (497); ([4]p.)
  - Cockburn, Henry. A.L.s.(H. Cockburn) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London 2 Mar [1893]., (498); ([4]p.)
  - Cockburn, Henry. A.L.s.(H. Cockburn) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chungking, 12 Aug [1889]., (499); [10]p.
  - Cobkburn, Henry. A. Petition of Liu-san to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Tieatsin, Sep 1889., (500); ([2]p.)
  - Cockburn, Henry. A.L.s.(Henry Cockburn) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 15 Nov [1891]., (501); ([8]p.)
  - Codman, Julian, 1870-1932. Typed L.s.(Julian Codman) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Boston, 23 Feb 1904., (502); 1l.
  - Cole, Fay Cooper, 1881- Typed L.s.(Fay Cooper Cole) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Chicago, 14 Sep 1914., (503); 1l.
  - Colegrove, Kenneth, 1886- A. Draft "A chapter in the Tragedy of Shantung"; Cambridge, [191-?] [7]l., (504)
  - Colegrove, Kenneth, 1886- A. Draft "John Jay and William Woodville Rockhill"; [n.p., 191-?] [16]l., (505)
  - Colegrove, Kenneth, 1886- A.L.s.(Kenneth Colegrove) to [Norman Dwight] Harris; Evanston, 28 Jun 1921., (506); [2]p.
    Also: A. Questions for Mr. Alfred E. Hippisley; Evanston, [n.d.] ([3]p.)
  - Coles, John. A.L.s.(John Coles) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London, 5 Jan 1894., (507); ([3]p.)
  - Coles, John. A.L.s.(John Coles) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 26 Feb 1894, (508); ([3]p.)
  - Coles, John. A.L.s.(John Coles) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 31 Mar 1894, (509); ([3]p.)
  - Collins, Robert M. A.L.s.(Robert Collins) to [John Gardner] Coolidge; [n.p., 1906], (510); ([4]p.)
  - Collins, Robert M. A.L.s.(R. M. Collins) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., 1906], (511); ([1]p.)
  - Collins, Robert M. A.L.s.(R. M. Collins) to [John Gardner] Coolidge; Peking, [1906], (512); ([4]p.)
  - Collins, Robert M. A.L.s.(R. M. Collins) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, [1906], (513); ([1]p.)
  - Collins, Robert M. A.L.s. (R. M. Collins) to [John Gardner] Coolidge; [Peking, 1906], (514); ([5]p.)
  - Collins, Robert M. A.L.s.(Collins) to [John Gardner] Coolidge; Peking, [1906], (515); 1l.
  - Collins, Robert M. Typed L.s.(Robert M. Collins) to [John Gardner] Coolidge; Peking, 11 May 1906., (516); 3l.
  - Collins, Robert M. A.L.s.(Robert M. Collins) to [John Gardner] Coolidge; Peking, 12 May 1906., (517); 2l.
  - Coleman, Leighton, bp. 1837-1908. A.L.s.(Leighton Coleman) to "My dear General" [?]; Wilmington, 4 Jun 1897., (518); ([1]p.)
    Enclosed: A.L.s.(Wm. Langford) to Bishop [Leighton] Coleman; New York, 1 Jun 1897. [2]p.
  - Coleman, William Emmette. A.L.s.(Wm. Emmette Coleman) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; San Francisco, 30 May 1890., (519); ([4]p.)
  - Coleman, William Emmette. A.L.s.(Wm. E. Coleman) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; San Francisco, 19 Jun 1890., (520); ([3]p.)
  - Coleman, William Emmette. A.L.s.(Wm. E. Coleman) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; San Francisco, 23 Jun 1890., (521); ([3]p.)
  - Coltman, Robert. A.L.s.(Robert Coltman, M.D.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Victoria Embankment, 3 Aug 1902., (522); ([3]p.)
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. Telegram message s.(Conger) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Berlin, 28 Dec [?], (523); 1l.
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. A.L.s.(E. H. Conger) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, [190-?], (524); ([4]p.)
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. Typed Copy of L.s.(E. H. Conger) to "Mr. Tewksbury"; Peking, 1 Sep 1900., (525); 1l.
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. A.L.s.(E. H. Conger) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 16 Mar 1901., (526); [3]p.
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. A.L.s.(E. H. Conger) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Des Moines, 2 Jul 1901., (527); [4]p.
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. A.L.s.(E. H. Conger) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 2 Sep 1901, (528); ([3]p.)
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. A.L.s.(E. H. Conger) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 2 Feb 1902, (529); ([1]p.)
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. Typed L.s.(E. H. Conger) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 24 May 1902., (530); 3l.
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. Typed L.s.(Conger) to "Secretary of State"; Peking, 25 Oct 1903., (531); 3l.
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. Typed L.s.(E. H. Conger) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 14 Dec 1903., (532); 1l.
  - Conger, Edwin Hurd, 1843-1907. A.L.s.(E. H. Conger) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 20 Apr 1905., (533); 3l.
  - Coolidge, Archibald Cary, 1866-1928. A.L.s.(Archibald Cary Coolidge) to [William Woodville] Rockhill Cambridge, 28 Nov [1894]., (533a); ([4]p.)
  - Coolidge, John Gardner, 1863- A.L.s.(John Gardner Coolidge) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Boston, 10 Nov 1914., (534); ([3]p.)
  - Coolidge, John Gardner, 1863- A.L.s.(John Gardner Coolidge) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; On board the "Lusitania", 12 Dec [1914]., (535); ([4]p.)
  - Colquhoun, Archibald Rose, 1848-1914. A.L.s.(Archibald R. Colquhoun) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Rochester, 8 Mar 1903., (536); ([3]p.)
  - Colquhoun, Archibald Rose, 1848-1914. A.L.s.(A. R. Colquhoun) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Rochester, 14 Mar 1903., (537); ([3]p.)
  - Comegys, Benjamin Bartis, 1819-1901. A.L.s.(B. B. Comegys) to [Thomas] C. Rockhill; Philadelphia, 22 Feb 1854., (538); ([3]p.)
  - Conkling, Alfred Ronald, 1850-1917. A.L.s.(A. R. Conkling) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 24 Dec 1892., (539); [2]p.
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 24 Jun 1896., (540); ([3]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 31 Jan 1898., (541); ([4]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925 A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville]Rockhill; Paris, 23 Mar 1900., (542); ([2]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 14 May 1900., (543); ([1]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 6 Apr 1902., (544); ([2]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 28 Oct 1904., (545); ([3]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 8 Dec 1909., (546); ([2]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 16 Dec 1909., (547); ([2]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; On board the "Cordillere", 29 Apr 1910., (548); ([2]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A. card s.(Henri Cordier to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 2 Dec 1910., (549); [2]p.
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 31 Dec 1911., (550); ([2]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 2 Sep 1912., (551); ([1]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 20 Dec 1913, (552); ([2]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 15 Jul 1914., (553); ([1]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 9 Sep 1914., (554); ([1]p.)
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Paris, 29 Jan 1916., (555); ([2]p.)
    Enclosed: Ms. Copy of speech of M. Emile Chatelain; [Paris] 11 Dec [1916 [3]p. In French.
  - Cordier, Henri, 1849-1925. A.L.s.(Henri Cordier) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 23 Dec 1895., (556); ([2]p.)
  - Conling, Samuel, 1859-1922. A.L.s.(Samuel Conling) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 2 Feb 1914., (557); 1l.
  - Cope, Caleb, 1797-1888. A.L.s.(C. Cope) to W. D. Lewis; [n.p.] 11 Mar [1855]., (558); ([1]p.)
  - Couman, A. A.L.s.(A. Couman) to [?]; Peking, 18-30 Dec 1887., (559); ([3]p.)
  - Couman, A. A.L.s.(A.Couman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 7.19 Sep 1889., (559a); ([4]p.)
  - Courant, Maurice, 1865-1935. A. card s. (Maurice Courant) to [?]; St. Alban-Leysse, 30 Aug 1913., (560); [2]p.
  - Coville, Frederick V. Typed Copy of L.s. (Frederick V. Coville) to Herbert Putnam; Washington, 24 Nov 1906., (561); 1l.
  - Cowles, Anna (Roosevelt). A.L.s.(Anna Roosevelt Cowles) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Farmington, 24 Jan 1915., (562); ([4]p.)
  - Craig, Austin, 1824-1881. Typed L.s. (Austin Craig) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Nagasaki, 11 May 1914., (563); 2l.
  - Crane, Charles R. A.L.s.(Charles R. Crane) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chicago, 2 Mar [1904], (564); ([2]p.)
  - Cridler, Thomas W. Typed L.(Thos.W.Cridler) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 11 Oct 1897., (564a); 4l.
    Enclosure: Typed "Extract from 'The Acropolis,' September 4, 1897. Translation." 1l.
  - Cridler,Thomas W. Typed L.(Thos. W.Cridler) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 21 Oct 1897., (564b); 3l.
  - Crosby, John Schuyler, 1835-1914. A.L.s.(Jhn. Schuyler Crosby) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Albany, 28 Feb [1896]., (565); ([1]p.)
  - Crossett, J. A.L.s.(J. Crossett) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 25 Jan [?], (566); [2]p.
  - Crossett, J. A.L.s.(J. Crossett) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mongolia Grassland, [1884], (567); ([4]p.)
  - Crossett, J. A.L.s.(J. C.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 6 Dec 1884. [2]p, (568)
  - Crossett, J. A.L.s.(J. C.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 14 Jan [?], (569); ([2]p.)
  - Crowninshield, A. S. Typed L.s. (A. S. Crowninshield) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 20 Mar 1902., (570); ([1]p.)
  - Culin, Stewart. A.L.s.(Stewart Culin) to [William Woodgille] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 6 Dec 1895., (571); [2]p.
  - Cullum, George Washington, 1809-1892. A.L.s.(Geo. W. Cullum) to "My dear General" [i.e. James H. Wilson]; New York, 7 Aug 1888., (572); ([2]p.)
  - Cullum, George Washington, 1809-1892. A.L.s.(G. W. Cullum) to [James] H. Wilson; New York, 18 Oct 1889., (573); 1l.
    On verso: A.L.s. (James H. Wilson) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 19 Oct [1889]. 1l.
  - Curtin, Jeremiah, 1840-1906. A.L.s.(Jeremiah Curtin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Bristol, Vt., 12 May 1902., (574); ([2]p.)
  - Curtin, Jeremiah, 1840-1906. A.L.s.(Jeremiah Curtin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Bristol, Vt., 23 Jun 1902., (575); ([2]p.)
  - Curtin, Jeremiah, 1840-1906. A.L.s.(Jeremiah Curtin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Bristol, Vt., 1 Jul 1902., (576); ([3]p.)
  - Curtin, Jeremiah, 1840-1906. A.L.s.(Jeremiah Curtin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Bristol, Vt., 15 Jul 1902., (577); ([2]p.)
  - Curtin, Jeremiah, 1840-1906. A.L.s.(Jeremiah Curtin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Bristol, Vt., 17 Jul 1902., (578); ([1]p.)
  - Curtin, Jeremiah, 1840-1906. A.L.s.(Jeremiah Curtin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Redding, California, 18 Nov 1902., (579); ([2]p.)
  - Curtin, Jeremiah, 1840-1906. A.L.s.(Jeremiah Curtin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 1 May 1903., (580); ([2]p.)
  - Curtis, William Eleroy, 1850-1911. Typed L.s. (William E. Curtin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Washington] 17 Apr 1897., (581); 1l.
  - Curzon of Kedleston, George Nathaniel Curzon, 1st marquess, 1859-1925. A.L.s.(George Curzon) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 24 Apr 1895., (582); ([2]p.)
  - Curzon, of Kedleston, George Nathaniel Curzon, 1st marquess, 1859-1925. Typed L.s. (Curzon of Kedleston) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; London, 28 Mar 1911., (583); [2]p.
  - Dabney, Charles W. A.L.s.(Chas.W.Dabney Jr.) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 14 Feb 1896., (583a); ([4]p.)
  - Daiber-Jaeschke, W. A.Postcard s.(W.Daiber-Jaeschke) to [William Woodville Rockhill] Herrnhut, 20 May [1883]., (583b)
  - Dalton, J. T. A.L.s.(J. T. Dalton) to [John] [Otway] [Percy] Bland; London, 26 Apr 1912., (584); 1l.
  - Dalton, J. T. A.L.s.(J. T. Dalton) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 14 Jun 1912., (585); ([1]p.)
  - Daly, Charles Patrick, 1816-1899. A.L.s.(Chas. P. Daly) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 28 Nov 1890., (586); ([2]p.)
  - Daly, H. Typed (c.c.) s. (H. Daly) to Dr. E. Schlagintweit; Simla, 1 Oct 1902., (587); 1l.
  - Dana, Charles Anderson, 1819-1897. Ms.L.s.(C. A. Dana) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 10 Jun 1891., (588); ([2]p.)
  - Dana, Charles Anderson, 1819-1897. Ms.L.s.(C. A. Dana) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 9 Apr 1894., (589); ([1]p.)
  - Davis, Cushman Kellogg, 1838-1900. Typed L.s.(C. K. Davis) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington. 23 Jul 1900., (590); ([1]p.)
  - Davis, D. A. A.L.s.(D. A. Davis) to [William Woodville Rockhill and Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; [n.p.] 3 Mar 1914., (591); ([4]p.)
  - Davis, John Chandler Bancroft, 1822-1907. A.L.s.(J. C. Bancroft Davis) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 12 Jan [1894]., (592); ([2]p.)
  - Davis, Richard Harding, 1864-1916. A.L.s.(Richard Harding Davis) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, [189-?], (593); ([4]p.)
  - Davis, Richard Harding, 1864-1916. A.L.s.(Richard Harding Davis) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 19 Dec [1893], (594); ([3]p.)
  - Davis, Richard Harding, 1864-1916. Typed L.s.(Richard Harding Davis) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 22 Oct 1895., (595); 3l.
  - Davis, Richard Harding, 1864-1916. A.L.s. (Richard Harding Davis) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 5 Mar [1897], (596); ([2]p.)
  - Davis, Richard Harding, 1864-1916. A.L.s.(Richard Harding Davis) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Marion, [1914], (596a); ([3]p.)
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T. W. Rhys Davids) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; [London] 30 May 1883., (597); ([4]p.)
    Enclosed: A. postcard s. (Rh. D.) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; [London, 30 May 1883] [1]p. Addressed on p. [2]
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T. W. Rhys Davids) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, 12 Dec [189-?], (598); 2l.
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T. W. Rhys Davids) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 10 Jul 1890., (599); ([8]p.)
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T. W. Rhys Davids) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 3 Nov 1890., (600); ([4]p.)
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T. W. Rhys Davids) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 15 Nov [1890]., (601); ([7]p.)
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T. W. Rhys Davids) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 1 Dec 1890., (602); ([4]p.)
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T. W. Rhys Davids) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 10 Mar [1893]., (603); ([4]p.)
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T. W. Rhys Davids) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 26 Nov 1894., (604); ([4]p.)
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T. W. Rhys Davids) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 19 Apr 1895., (605); ([3]p.)
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T. W. Rhys Davids) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 14 May [1895]., (606); ([4]p.)
  - Davids, Thomas William Rhys, 1843-1923. A.L.s.(T.W.Rhys Davids) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London 13 Dec 1897., (606a); ([4]p.)
  - Davis, William Morris, 1850-1934. A.L.s.(W. M. Davis) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 28 Feb 1903., (607); 1l.
  - Davis, William Morris, 1850-1934. A.L.s.(W. M. Davis) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 13 Mar 1903., (608); 1l.
  - Davis, William Morris, 1850-1934. A.L.s.(W. M. Davis) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 2 Sep 1903., (609); ([2]p.)
  - Davis, William Morris, 1850-1934. A.L.s.(W. M. Davis) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 28 Oct 1903., (610); 1l.
  - Davis, William Morris, 1850-1934. A.L.s.(W. M. Davis) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 27 Nov 1904., (611); 1l.
  - Davis, William Morris, 1850-1934. A.L.s.(W. M. Davis) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 2 Dec 1904., (612); 2l.
  - Davis, William Morris, 1850-1934. A.L.s.(W. M. Davis) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 8 Mar 1905., (613); 1l.
  - Davis, William Morris, 1850-1934. A.L.s.(W. M. Davis) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Johannesburg, 31 Aug 1905., (614); ([3]p.)
  - Davis, William Morris, 1850-1934. Typed L.s.(W. M. Davis) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 26 May 1906., (615); 1l.
  - Davis, William Morris, 1850-1934. Typed L.s.(W. M. Davis) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 26 May 1912., (616); 1l.
  - Day, William Rufus, 1849-1923. Typed L.s.(William R. Day) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, [n.d.], (617); 1l.
  - Day, William Rufus, 1849-1923. Typed L.s.(William R. Day) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 16 May 1898., (618); ([1]p.)
  - De Kay, Charles, 1848- A.L.s.(Charles de Kay) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Berlin, 12 Nov 1895., (619); ([2]p.)
  - DeKoven, Anna (Farwell) A.L.s.(Anna deKoven) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Bar Harbor, 14 Aug 1910., (619a); ([5]p.)
  - Delecray, Marie. A.L.s.(Marie) to "Daisy and Madame Hoppin"; Geneve, 4 Jul [1913], (620); [2]p.
  - Delecray, Marie. A.L.s.(Marie Delecray) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Geneve] 4 Jun [1913], (621); [2]p.
  - Delecray, Marie. Typed telegram s.(Marie Delecray) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Geneve, 11 Apr [1912]., (622); 1l.
  - Delecray, Marie. Telegram s.(Marie Delecray) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Pera, 5 Jun [1913], (623); 1l.
  - Delecray, Marie. A.L.s.(Marie Delecray) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mollesulaz, 18 Jun [1913], (624); ([4]p.)
  - Delecray, Marie. A.L.s.(Marie Delecray) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mollesulaz, 15 Aug 1913., (625); [2]p.
  - Delecray, Marie. A.L.s.(Marie Delecray) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Mollesulaz, 1 Jan [1914]., (626); ([4]p.)
  - Delcasse, Theophile, 1852-1923. Typed Copy of L.s.(Delcasse) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 16 Dec 1899., (627); 1l.
  - DeMeuil, Henry N. A.L.s.(Henry N. DeMeuil) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Camp Bathang, 16 May 1907., (628); ([2]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(C. Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 10 Sep [188-?], (629); 1l.
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(C. Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., 1886], (630); 1l.
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Hong Kong, 28 Apr 1886., (630a); ([4]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Fou-Cho 10 May 1886., (630b); ([3]p.)
  - Denbym Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shangha 20 May 1886., (630c); ([3]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shangha 20 Jun 1886., (630d); ([4]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Tientse 25 Jun [1886]., (630e); ([4]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Tientse 26 Jun 1886., (630f); ([3]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 6 Sep 1886., (630g); ([3]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 28 Nov 1886., (631); ([2]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(C.Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.,1887], (631a); (2l.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 14 Jan 1887., (632); ([2]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Roclhill; Peking, 26 Jan 1887., (633); ([2]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(C.Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 11 Mar 1887., (633a); ([4]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 6 Apr 1887., (633b); 1l.
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 19 Apr 1887., (633c); ([3]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 26 Apr 1887., (633d); ([3]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 8 Aug 1887., (634); ([1]p.)
  - Denby, Charles, 1830-1904. A.L.s.(Charles Denby) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 27 Aug 1887., (635); 1l.